Finding Aid for Jeffrey R. Parsons papers, 1960-2013
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
- Archaeological Sites and Projects 1966-2010
  - Chalco-Xochimilco 1972
    - Site Reports
      - XW-Az-2 Xochimilco West 21-E-SE JRP 1972 (Box 18)
      - XW-Az-3 Xochimilco West 21-E-SE JRP 1972 (Box 18)
      - XW-Az-4 Xochimilco West 21-E-SW JRP 1972 (Box 18)
      - XW-Az-5 Xochimilco West 21-F-NW JRP 1972 (Box 18)
      - XW-Az-6 Xochimilco West 21-F-NW JRP 1972 (Box 18)
      - XW-Az-7 Xochimilco West 21-F-SW JRP 1972 (Box 18)
      - XW-Az-8 Xochimilco West 21-D-NW JRP 1972 (Box 18)
      - XW-Az-9 Xochimilco West 21-C-SW JRP 1972 (Box 18)
      - XW-Az-10 Xochimilco West 21-B-NE JRP 1972 (Box 18)
      - XW-Az-11 Xochimilco West 21-B-NE JRP 1972 (Box 18)
      - XW-Az-12 Xochimilco West 46-A-SW Cerro Zacaltepetl JRP 1972 (Box 18)
      - XW-Az-13 Xochimilco West 13-A-NE JRP 1972 (Box 18)
      - XW-Az-14 Xochimilco West 13-C-SE JRP 1972 (Box 18)
      - XW-Az-15 Xochimilco West 13-C-SW JRP 1972 (Box 18)
      - XW-Az-16 Xochimilco West 13-C-SW JRP 1972 (Box 18)
      - XW-Az-17 Xochimilco West 14-A-SW JRP 1972 (Box 18)
      - XW-Az-18 Xochimilco West 14-A-SE JRP 1972 (Box 18)
      - XW-Az-19 Xochimilco West 14-B-NE JRP 1972 (Box 18)
      - XW-Az-20 Xochimilco West 14-B-NE JRP 1972 (Box 18)
      - XW-Az-21 Xochimilco West 14-B-NE JRP 1972 (Box 18)
      - XW-Az-22 Xochimilco West 14-B-SW JRP 1972 (Box 18)
      - XW-Az-23 Xochimilco West 14-B-SW JRP 1972 (Box 18)
      - XW-Az-24 Xochimilco West 14-D-SW JRP 1972 (Box 18)
      - XW-Az-25 Xochimilco West 14-D-SW JRP 1972 (Box 18)
      - XW-Az-26 Xochimilco West 14-D-SW JRP 1972 (Box 18)
      - XW-Az-27 Xochimilco West 14-D-SW JRP 1972 (Box 18)
      - XW-Az-28 Xochimilco West 14-D-NE JRP 1972 (Box 18)
      - Miscellaneous Calculations for Xochimilco Data, 2 folders (Box 18)
      - Tula Spindle Whorl Photos (Dick Dieht's) 1972 (Box 18)
      - Valley of Mexico-Site Numbers-Locations-(Mary) 1972 (Box 18)
      - 1:25,000 reductions (Mary) (Box 18)
      - Chalco-Xochimilco (Mary) 1972 (Box 18)
      - Early Formative (Mary) 1972 (Box 18)
      - Middle Formative (Mary) 1972 (Box 18)
      - Late Formative (Mary) 1972 (Box 18)
      - Terminal Formative (Mary) 1972 (Box 18)
      - Classic (Mary) 1972 (Box 18)
      - Early Toltec (Mary) 1972 (Box 18)
      - Late Toltec (Mary) 1972 (Box 18)
      - Aztec (Mary) 1972 (Box 18)
      - Am-?-1 (Mary) 1972 (Box 18)
      - Am-F-1 (Mary) 1972 (Box 18)
      - Am-F-2 (Mary) 1972 (Box 18)
      - Am-F-3 (Mary) 1972 (Box 18)
      - Am-F-4 (Mary) 1972 (Box 18)
      - Am-F-5 (Mary) 1972 (Box 18)
      - Am-F-6 (Mary) 1972 (Box 18)
      - Am-F-7 (Mary) 1972 (Box 18)
      - Am-F-8 (Mary) 1972 (Box 18)
      - Am-F-9 (Mary) 1972 (Box 18)
      - Am-F-10 (Mary) 1972 (Box 18)
      - Am-F-11 (Mary) 1972 (Box 18)
      - Am-F-12 (Mary) 1972 (Box 18)
      - Am-F-13 (Mary) 1972 (Box 18)
      - Am-F-14 (Mary) 1972 (Box 18)
      - Am-F-15 (Mary) 1972 (Box 18)
      - Am-MF-1 (Mary) 1972 (Box 18)
      - Am-MF-2 (Mary) 1972 (Box 18)
      - Am-LF-2 (Mary) 1972 (Box 18)
      - Am-LF-2 (Mary) 1972 (Box 18)
      - Am-LF-3 (Mary) 1972 (Box 18)
      - Am-LF-4 (Mary) 1972 (Box 18)
      - Am-LF-4 (Mary) 1972 (Box 18)
      - Am-LF-5 (Mary) 1972 (Box 18)
      - Am-LF-6 (Mary) 1972 (Box 18)
      - Am-LF-16 5-F, 5-D, 5-E (Mary) 1972 (Box 18)
      - Am-TF-1 6A-SE (Mary) 1972 (Box 18)
      - Am-TF-2 Combined with Am-TF-2(W) (Mary) 1972 (Box 18)
      - Am-TF-3 7C-NE (Mary) 1972 (Box 18)
      - Am-TF-4 (Mary) 1972 (Box 18)
      - Am-TF-4 (Mary) 1972 (Box 18)
      - Am-TF-5 (Mary) 1972 (Box 18)
      - Am-TF-6 (Mary) 1972 (Box 18)
      - Am-Cl-1 (Mary) 1972 (Box 18)
      - Am-Cl-2 (Mary) 1972 (Box 18)
      - Am-Cl-3 (Mary) 1972 (Box 18)
      - Am-Cl-4 (Mary) 1972 (Box 18)
      - Am-Cl-5 (Mary) 1972 (Box 18)
      - Am-Cl-6 (Mary) 1972 (Box 18)
      - Am-Cl-7 (Mary) 1972 (Box 18)
      - Am-Cl-8 (Mary) 1972 (Box 18)
      - Am-Cl-9 (Mary) 1972 (Box 18)
      - Am-Cl-10 (Mary) 1972 (Box 18)
      - Am-Cl-11 (Mary) 1972 (Box 18)
      - Am-Cl-12 (Mary) 1972 (Box 18)
      - Am-Cl-13 (Mary) 1972 (Box 18)
      - Am-Cl-14 (Mary) 1972 (Box 18)
      - Am-Cl-15 (Mary) 1972 (Box 18)
      - Am-Cl-16 (Mary) 1972 (Box 18)
      - Am-Cl-17 (Mary) 1972 (Box 18)
      - Am-ET-1 (Mary) 1972 (Box 18)
      - Am-ET-2 (Mary) 1972 (Box 18)
      - Am-LT-1 (Mary) 1972 (Box 18)
      - Am-T-2 (Mary) 1972 (Box 18)
      - Am-T-3 (Mary) 1972 (Box 18)
      - Am-T-4 (Mary) 1972 (Box 18)
      - Am-T-5 (Mary) 1972 (Box 18)
      - Am-LT-6 (Mary) 1972 (Box 18)
      - Am-LT-7 6B-Center (Mary) 1972 (Box 18)
      - Am-LT-8 7B-SE (Mary) 1972 (Box 18)
      - Am-LT-9 (Mary) 1972 (Box 18)
      - Am-LT-10 (Mary) 1972 (Box 18)
      - Am-LT-11 (Mary) 1972 (deleted) (Box 18)
      - Am-LT-12 (Mary) 1972 (Box 18)
      - Am-LT-13 (Mary) 1972 (Box 18)
      - Am-LT-14 (Mary) 1972 (Box 18)
      - Am-LT-15 (Mary) 1972 (Box 18)
      - Am-LT-16 (Mary) 1972 (Box 18)
      - Am-LT-17 (Mary) 1972 (Box 18)
      - Am-LT-18 (Mary) 1972 (Box 18)
      - Am-Az-1 (Mary) 1972 (Box 18)
      - Am-Az-2 (Mary) 1972 (Box 19)
      - Am-Az-3 (Mary) 1972 (Box 19)
      - Am-Az-4 (Mary) 1972 (Box 19)
      - Am-Az-5 (Mary) 1972 (Box 19)
      - Am-Az-6 (Mary) 1972 (Box 19)
      - Am-Az-7 (Mary) 1972 (Box 19)
      - Am-Az-8 (Mary) 1972 (Box 19)
      - Am-Az-9 (Mary) 1972 (Box 19)
      - Am-Az-10 (Mary) 1972 (Box 19)
      - Am-Az-11 (Mary) 1972 (Box 19)
      - Am-Az-12 (Mary) 1972 (Box 19)
      - Am-Az-13 (Mary) 1972 (Box 19)
      - Am-Az-14 (Mary) 1972 (Box 19)
      - Am-Az-15 (Mary) 1972 (Box 19)
      - Am-Az-16 (Mary) 1972 (Box 19)
      - Am-Az-17 (Mary) 1972 (Box 19)
      - Am-Az-18 (Mary) 1972 (Box 19)
      - Am-Az-19 (Mary) 1972 (Box 19)
      - Am-Az-20 (Mary) 1972 (Box 19)
      - Am-Az-21 (Mary) 1972 (Box 19)
      - Am-Az-22 (Mary) 1972 (Box 19)
      - Am-Az-23 (Mary) 1972 (Box 19)
      - Am-Az-24 (Mary) 1972 (Box 19)
      - Am-Az-25 (Mary) 1972 (Box 19)
      - Am-Az-26 6-A-NE (Mary) 1972 (Box 19)
      - Am-Az-27 6-A-SE (Mary) 1972 (Box 19)
      - Am-Az-28 (Mary) 1972 (Box 19)
      - Am-Az-29 (Mary) 1972 (Box 19)
      - Am-Az-30 (Mary) 1972 (Box 19)
      - Am-Az-31 (Mary) 1972 (Box 19)
      - Am-Az-32 6-A-NW (Mary) 1972 (Box 19)
      - Am-Az-33 (Mary) 1972 (Box 19)
      - Am-Az-34 6-A-NE (Mary) 1972 (Box 19)
      - Am-Az-35 6-A-NW (Mary) 1972 (Box 19)
      - Am-Az-36 6CNE (Mary) 1972 (Box 19)
      - Am-Az-37 7-D-NE, NW (Mary) 1972 (Box 19)
      - Am-Az-38 7B-SE (Mary) 1972 (Box 19)
      - Am-Az-39 7B NW, NE, SW (Mary) 1972 (Box 19)
      - Am-Az-40 (Mary) 1972 (Box 19)
      - Am-Az-41 7BNW (Mary) 1972 (Box 19)
      - Am-Az-42 7BNE (Mary) 1972 (Box 19)
      - Am-Az-43 (Mary) 1972 (Box 19)
      - Am-A2-44 (Mary) 1972 (Box 19)
      - Am-A2-45 (Mary) 1972 (Box 19)
      - Am-Az-46 7DNW/ 7CSW (Mary) 1972 (Box 19)
      - Am-Az-47 7CSE (Mary) 1972 (Box 19)
      - Am-Az-48 (Mary) 1972 (Box 19)
      - Am-Az-49 (Mary) 1972 (Box 19)
      - Am-Az-50 (Mary) 1972 (Box 19)
      - Am-Az-51 (Mary) 1972 (Box 19)
      - Am-Az-52 (Mary) 1972 (Box 19)
      - Am-A2-53 (Mary) 1972 (Box 19)
      - Am-Az-54 (Mary) 1972 (Box 19)
      - Am-Az-55 (Mary) 1972 (Box 19)
      - Am-Az-56 (Mary) 1972 (Box 19)
      - Am-Az-57 (Mary) 1972 (Box 19)
      - Am-Az-58 (Mary) 1972 (Box 19)
      - Am-Az-59 (Mary) 1972 (Box 19)
      - Am-Az-60 (Mary) 1972 (not made a site) (Box 19)
      - Am-Az-61 (Mary) 1972 (Box 19)
      - Am-Az-62 (Mary) 1972 (Box 19)
      - Am-Az-63 (Mary) 1972 (Box 19)
      - Am-Az-64 (Mary) 1972 (Box 19)
      - XE-Az-1 (Mary) 1972 (Box 19)
      - XE-Az-2 (Mary) 1972 (Box 19)
      - XE-Az-3 (Mary) 1972 (Box 19)
      - XE-Az-4 (Mary) 1972 (Box 19)
      - XE-Az-6 (Mary) 1972 (Box 19)
      - XE-Az-5 (Mary) 1972 (Box 19)
      - XE-Az-7 (Mary) 1972 (Box 19)
      - XE-Az-8 (Mary) 1972 (Box 19)
      - XE-Az-9 (Mary) 1972 (Box 19)
      - XE-Az-10 (Mary) 1972 (Box 19)
      - XE-Az-11 (Mary) 1972 (Box 19)
      - XE-Az-12 (Mary) 1972 (Box 19)
      - XE-Az-13 (Mary) 1972 (Box 19)
      - XE-Az-14 (Mary) 1972 (Box 19)
      - XE-Az-15 (Mary) 1972 (Box 19)
      - XE-Az-16 (Mary) 1972 (Box 19)
      - XE-Az-17 (Mary) 1972 (Box 19)
      - XE-Az-18 (Mary) 1972 (Box 19)
      - XE-Az-19 (Mary) 1972 (Box 19)
      - XE-Az-20 (Mary) 1972 (Box 19)
      - XE-Az-21 (Mary) 1972 (Box 19)
      - XE-Az-21 (Mary) 1972 (Box 19)
      - XE-Az-22 (Mary) 1972 (Box 19)
      - XE-Az-23 (Mary) 1972 (Box 19)
      - XE-Az-24 (Mary) 1972 (Box 19)
      - XE-Az-25 (Mary) 1972 (Box 19)
      - XE-Az-26 (Mary) 1972 (Box 19)
      - XE-Az-27 (Mary) 1972 (Box 19)
      - XE-Az-28 (Mary) 1972 (Box 19)
      - XE-Az-29 (Mary) 1972 (Box 19)
      - XE-Az-30 (Mary) 1972 (Box 19)
      - XE-Az-31 (Mary) 1972 (Box 19)
      - XE-Az-32 (Mary) 1972 (Box 19)
      - XE-Az-33 (Mary) 1972 (Box 19)
      - XE-Az-34 (Mary) 1972 (Box 19)
      - XE-Az-35 (Mary) 1972 (Box 19)
      - XE-Az-36 (Mary) 1972 (Box 19)
      - XE-Az-37 (Mary) 1972 (Box 19)
      - XE-Az-38 (Mary) 1972 (Box 19)
      - XE-EF-1 (Mary) 1972 (Box 19)
      - XE-EF-2 (Mary) 1972 (Box 19)
      - XE-LF-1 (Mary) 1972 (Box 19)
      - XE-LF-2 (Mary) 1972 (Box 19)
      - XE-TF-1 (Mary) 1972 (Box 19)
      - XE-TF-2 (Mary) 1972 (Box 19)
      - XE-Cl-1 (Mary) 1972 (Box 19)
      - XE-Cl-2 (Mary) 1972 (Box 19)
      - XE-Cl-3 (Mary) 1972 (Box 19)
      - XE-Cl-4 (Mary) 1972 (Box 19)
      - XE-Cl-5 (Mary) 1972 (Box 19)
      - XE-ET-1 (Mary) 1972 (Box 19)
      - XE-ET-2 (Mary) 1972 (Box 19)
      - XE-ET-3 (Mary) 1972 (Box 19)
      - XE-ET-4 53-D-NE 53-C (Mary) 1972 (Box 19)
      - XE-LT-1 (Mary) 1972 (Box 19)
      - XE-LT-2 (Mary) 1972 (Box 19)
      - XW-Az-29 51-D-NE Xochimilco West (JRP) 1972 (Box 19)
      - XW-Az-30 51-D-NE Xochimilco West (JRP) 1972 (Box 19)
      - XW-Az-31 51-F-NE Xochimilco West (JRP) 1972 (Box 19)
      - XW-Az-32 52-A-SE Xochimilco West (JRP) 1972 (Box 19)
      - XW-Az-33 21-D-SE Xochimilco West (JRP) 1972 (Box 19)
      - XW-Az-34 52-D-NW Xochimilco West (JRP) 1972 (Box 19)
      - XW-Az-35 52-F-North Xochimilco West (JRP) 1972 (Box 19)
      - XW-Az-36 52-F-North Xochimilco West (JRP) 1972 (Box 19)
      - XW-Az-37 52-D-NW Xochimilco West (JRP) 1972 (Box 19)
      - XW-Az-38 52-D-SE Xochimilco West (JRP) 1972 (Box 19)
      - XW-Az-39 57-A-SW Xochimilco West (JRP)1972 (Box 19)
      - XW-Az-40 57-A-SW Xochimilco West (JRP) 1972 (Box 19)
      - XW-Az-41 57-A-SE Xochimilco West (JRP) 1972 (Box 19)
      - XW-Az-42 52-D-NE Xochimilco West (JRP) 1972 (Box 19)
      - Valley of Mexico 1972 Location/ Features = Site Numbers Wenke 1972 (Box 19)
      - Late Formative (Wenke) 1972 (Box 19)
      - Terminal Formative (Wenke) 1972 (Box 19)
      - Classic (Wenke) 1972 (Box 19)
      - Early Toltec (Wenke) 1972 (Box 19)
      - Late Toltec (Wenke) 1972 (Box 19)
      - Aztec (Wenke) 1972 (Box 19)
      - Sites 1:25000 (Wenke) 1972 (Box 19)
      - Ch-LF-1 (W) 16-C-SW (Wenke) 1972 (Blanton Survey Area) (Box 19)
      - Ch-LF-2 (W) 16-C-NE (Wenke) 1972 (Blanton Survey Area) (Box 19)
      - Ch-LF-3 (W) 16-C-SW (Wenke) 1972 (Blanton Survey Area) (Box 19)
      - Ch-LF-4 (W) 23-F-S (Wenke) 1972 (Blanton Survey Area) (Box 19)
      - Am-LF-1 (W) (Wenke) 1972 (Box 19)
      - Am-LF-2 (W) (Wenke) 1972 (Box 19)
      - Am-LF-3 (W) (Wenke) 1972 (Box 19)
      - Am-LF-4 (W) (Wenke) 1972 (Box 19)
      - Am-LF-5 (W) (Wenke) 1972 (Box 19)
      - Am-LF-6 (W) (Wenke) 1972 (Box 19)
      - Am-LF-7 (W) (Wenke) 1972 (Box 19)
      - Ch-TF-1(W) (Wenke) 1972 (Box 19)
      - Am-TF-1 (Wenke) 1972 (Box 19)
      - Ch-Cl-1 (W) 16-C-NE (Wenke) 1972 (deleted-was in Blanton survey) (Box 19)
      - Ch-Cl-2 (W) 16-C-NE (Wenke) 1972 (deleted-was in Blanton survey) (Box 19)
      - Am-Cl-1 (W) (Wenke) 1972 (Box 19)
      - Am-Cl-2 (W) (Wenke) 1972 (Box 19)
      - Am-Cl-3 (W) (Wenke) 1972 (Box 19)
      - Am-Cl-4 (W) (Wenke) 1972 (Box 19)
      - Am-Cl-5 (W) 2-C-SE (Wenke) 1972 (Box 19)
      - Am-Cl-6 (W) (Wenke) 1972 (Box 19)
      - Ch-LT-1 (W) 32-H-NE (Wenke) 1972 (Box 19)
      - Ch-LT-2 (W) 32-H-NE (Wenke) 1972 (Box 19)
      - Ch-LT-3 (W) 32-H-SW (Wenke) 1972 (Box 19)
      - Ch-LT-4 (W) 32-H-NW (Wenke) 1972 (delete) (Box 19)
      - Ch-LT-5 (W) 32-H-NW (Wenke) 1972 (Box 19)
      - Ch-LT-6 (W) 32-H-SW (Wenke) 1972 (Box 19)
      - Ch-LT-7 (W) 32-H-SW (Wenke) 1972 (Box 19)
      - Ch-LT-8 (W) 32-G-NE (Wenke) 1972 (Box 19)
      - Ch-LT-9 (W) 32-G-NE (Wenke) 1972 (Box 19)
      - Ch-LT-10 (W) 32-G-NW (Wenke) 1972 (Box 19)
      - Ch-LT-11 (W) 24-B-NW (Wenke) 1972 (Box 19)
      - Ch-LT-12 (W) 32-H-SE (Wenke) 1972 (Box 19)
      - Ch-LT-13 (W) 16-B-SW (Wenke) 1972 (Box 19)
      - Am-Az-1 (W) (Wenke) 1972 (Box 19)
      - Am-Az-2 (W) (Wenke) 1972 (Box 19)
      - Am-Az-2 (W) (Wenke) 1972 (Box 19)
      - Am-Az-3 (W) (Wenke) 1972 (Box 19)
      - Am-Az-4 (W) (Wenke) 1972 (Box 19)
      - Am-Az-5 (W) (Wenke) 1972 (Box 19)
      - Ch-Az-1 (W) 32-H-NE (Wenke) 1972 (Box 19)
      - Ch-Az-2 (W) 32-H-NE (Wenke) 1972 (Box 19)
      - Ch-Az-3 (W) 32-H-SE (Wenke) 1972 (Box 19)
      - Ch-Az-4 (W) 32-H-SE (Wenke) 1972 (Box 19)
      - Ch-Az-5 (W) 32-H-SW (Wenke) 1972 (Box 19)
      - Ch-Az-6 (W) 32-H-SE (Wenke) 1972 (Box 19)
      - Ch-Az-7 (W) 32-H-NW (Wenke) 1972 (Box 19)
      - Ch-Az-8 (W) 32-H-SW (Wenke) 1972 (Box 19)
      - Ch-Az-9 (W) 32-H-SW (Wenke) 1972 (Box 19)
      - Ch-Az-10 (W) 32-H-SE (Wenke) 1972 (Box 19)
      - Ch-Az-11 (W) 32-H-SW (Wenke) 1972 (Box 19)
      - Ch-Az-12 (W) 32-H-SW (Wenke) 1972 (Box 19)
      - Ch-Az-13 (W) 32-H-NW (Wenke) 1972 (Box 19)
      - Ch-Az-14 (W) 32-H-SW (Wenke) 1972 (Box 19)
      - Ch-Az-15 (W) 32-H-SW (Wenke) 1972 (Box 20)
      - Ch-Az-16 (W) 32-H-SW (Wenke) 1972 (Box 20)
      - Ch-Az-17 (W) 32-H-NE (Wenke) 1972 (Box 20)
      - Ch-Az-18 (W) 32-G-NE (Wenke) 1972 (Box 20)
      - Ch-Az-19 (W) 32-G-NE (Wenke) 1972 (Box 20)
      - Ch-Az-20 (W) 32-G-NE (Wenke) 1972 (Box 20)
      - Ch-Az-21 (W) 32-G-SE (Wenke) 1972 (Box 20)
      - Ch-Az-22 (W) 32-G-SE (Wenke) 1972 (Box 20)
      - Ch-Az-23 (W) 32-G-SE (Wenke) 1972 (Box 20)
      - Ch-Az-24 (W) 32-G-NE (Wenke) 1972 (Box 20)
      - Ch-Az-25 (W) 32-G-NE (Wenke) 1972 (Box 20)
      - Ch-Az-26 (W) 32-G-NW (Wenke) 1972 (Box 20)
      - Ch-Az-27 (W) 32-G-NW (Wenke) 1972 (Box 20)
      - Ch-Az-28 (W) 32-G-NW (Wenke) 1972 (Box 20)
      - Ch-Az-29 (W) 32-G-NW (Wenke) 1972 (Box 20)
      - Ch-Az-30 (W) 32-G-NW (Wenke) 1972 (Box 20)
      - Ch-Az-31 (W) 32-G-SW (Wenke) 1972 (Box 20)
      - Ch-Az-32 (W) 24-B-NE (Wenke) 1972 (Box 20)
      - Ch-Az-33 (W) 24-B-NE (Wenke) 1972 (Box 20)
      - Ch-Az-34 (W) 24-B-SE (Wenke) 1972 (Box 20)
      - Ch-Az-35 (W) 24-B-SE (Wenke) 1972 (Box 20)
      - Ch-Az-36 (W) 24-B-NW (Wenke) 1972 (Box 20)
      - Ch-Az-37 (W) 24-B-NW (Wenke) 1972 (Box 20)
      - Ch-Az-38 (W) 24-B-NW (Wenke) 1972 (Box 20)
      - Ch-Az-39 (W) 24-B-NW (Wenke) 1972 (Box 20)
      - Ch-Az-40 (W) 24-B-SW (Wenke) 1972 (Box 20)
      - Ch-Az-41 (W) 24-B-SW (Wenke) 1972 (Box 20)
      - Ch-Az-42 (W) 24-B-SW (Wenke) 1972 (Box 20)
      - Ch-Az-43 (W) 24-B-SW (Wenke) 1972 (Box 20)
      - Ch-Az-44 (W) 32-G-NW (Wenke) 1972 (Box 20)
      - Ch-Az-45 (W) 24-A-SE (Wenke) 1972 (Box 20)
      - Ch-Az-46 (W) 24-A-SW (Wenke) 1972 (Box 20)
      - Ch-Az-47 (W) 24-A-SW (Wenke) 1972 (Box 20)
      - Ch-Az-48 (W) 24-A-SW (Wenke) 1972 (Box 20)
      - Ch-Az-49 (W) 24-A-NE (Wenke) 1972 (Box 20)
      - Ch-Az-50 (W) 24-A-NE (Wenke) 1972 (Box 20)
      - Ch-Az-51 (W) 24-A-NE, 16-B-SE (Wenke) 1972 (Box 20)
      - Ch-Az-52 (W) 16-C-SW (Wenke) 1972 (Box 20)
      - Ch-Az-53 (W) 24-D-NE (Wenke) 1972 (Box 20)
      - Ch-Az-54 (W) 24-D-NE (Wenke) 1972 (Box 20)
      - Ch-Az-55 (W) 24-D-SE (Wenke) 1972 (Box 20)
      - Ch-Az-56 (W) 24-D-SE (Wenke) 1972 (Box 20)
      - Ch-Az-57 (W) 24-D-SE (Wenke) 1972 (Box 20)
      - Ch-Az-58 (W) 24-D-SE (Wenke) 1972 (Box 20)
      - Ch-Az-59 (W) 24-D-SE (Wenke) 1972 (Box 20)
      - Ch-Az-60 (W) 24-D-SE (Wenke) 1972 (Box 20)
      - Ch-Az-61 (W) 24-D-SE (Wenke) 1972 (Box 20)
      - Ch-Az-62 (W) 24-D-SE (Wenke) 1972 (Box 20)
      - Ch-Az-63 (W) 24-C-E (Wenke) 1972 (Box 20)
      - Ch-Az-64 (W) 24-A-SE (Wenke) 1972 (Box 20)
      - Ch-Az-65 (W) 24-D-NE (Wenke) 1972 (Box 20)
      - Ch-Az-66 (W) 24-D-NE (Wenke) 1972 (Box 20)
      - Ch-Az-67 (W) 23-F-S (Wenke) 1972 (Box 20)
      - Ch-Az-68 (W) 23-F-S (Wenke) 1972 (Box 20)
      - Ch-Az-69 (W) 23-F-S (Wenke) 1972 (Box 20)
      - Ch-Az-70 (W) 23-F-S (Wenke) 1972 (Box 20)
      - Ameca Survey-Late Aztec 1972 (Box 20)
      - Ameca Survey-Early Aztec 1972 (Box 20)
      - Ameca Survey-Early Formative 1972 (Box 20)
      - Ameca Survey-Middle-Formative 1972 (Box 20)
      - Ameca Survey-Late Formative 1972 (Box 20)
      - Ameca Survey-Terminal Formative 1972 (Box 20)
      - Ameca Survey-Classic 1972 (Box 20)
      - Ameca Survey-Early Toltec 1972 (Box 20)
      - Ameca Survey-Late Toltec 1972 (Box 20)
      - Mexico 1972-Rapid Survey: Amecameca Region (Box 20)
      - Mexico 1972-Prahl 1:25,000 reductions (Box 20)
      - Mexico 1972-Photographs-Miscellaneous Shots (Rey) (Box 20)
      - Miscellaneous Sites, Notes (Box 20)
      - Prahl-Chalco-Xochimilco 1972 (Box 20)
      - Prahl-early Formative 1972 (Box 20)
      - Prahl-Late Formative 1972 (Box 20)
      - Prahl-Terminal formative (Box 20)
      - Prahl-Classic 1972 (Box 20)
      - Prahl-Early Toltec 1972 (Box 20)
      - Prahl-Late Toltec 1972 (Box 20)
      - Prahl-Aztec E & L 1972 (Box 20)
      - Ameca Survey-Location Summary-Survey Photo List Summary (Box 20)
    - Field Notebooks
      - Jeffrey Parsons, Book 1-A, 1-B 1972 (Box 20)
      - Mary Parsons, Book 1-A, 1-B, 2 1972 (Box 20)
      - Robert Wenke, Book 1 & 2 1972 (Box 20)
    - Sherd Profile Cards 1972 (Box 20)
  - Zumpango 1973
    The Zumpango 1973 sub series (3.25 linear feet) holds the site reports and notebooks along with ceramic analyses for the project. A number of indices for Zumpango photographic rolls are also part of the contents. Site notebooks data was gathered by Jeffrey and Mary Parsons. A third group of documents are map related materials. These are paper materials that were received with the maps for the Zumpango region and have been housed with the site materials.
    - Site Reports
      - Zu-LT-38 (J) 101-E-NW Zumpango East (Box 20)
      - Zu-LT-39 (J) 101-C-SE Zumpango-East (Box 20)
      - Zu-LT-40 (J) 101-C-SW Zumpango-East (Box 20)
      - Zu-LT-41 (J) 101-C-NW Zumpango-East (Box 20)
      - Zu-LT-42 (J) 101-F-NE Zumpango-East (Box 20)
      - Zu-LT-43 (J) 101-F-NE, 101-F-SE Zumpango-East (Box 20)
      - Zu-LT-44 (J) 101-F-SE, SW Zumpango-East (Box 20)
      - Zu-LT-45 (J) 101-F-SW Zumpango-East (Box 20)
      - Zu-LT-46 (J) 101-F-SW Zumpango-East (Box 20)
      - Zu-LT-47 (J) 101-F-NW Zumpango-East (Box 21)
      - Zu-LT-48 (J) 101-F-NW Zumpango-East (Box 21)
      - Zu-LT-49 (J) 101-D-NE Zumpango-East (Box 21)
      - Zu-LT-50 (J) 101-A-NE, NW Zumpango-East (Box 21)
      - Zu-LT-51 (J) 101-A-NE Zumpango-East (Box 21)
      - Zu-LT-52 (J) 101-A-NE Zumpango-East (Box 21)
      - Zu-LT-53 (J) 101-A-SE Zumpango-East (Box 21)
      - Zu-LT-54 (J) 101-B-SE, SW Zumpango-East (Box 21)
      - Zu-LT-55 (J) 101-B-SE, SW Zumpango-East (Box 21)
      - Zu-LT-56 (J) 101-A-NE Zumpango-East (Box 21)
      - Zu-LT-57 (J) 103-A-SE Zumpango-East (Box 21)
      - Zu-LT-58 (J) 103-A-SE Zumpango-East (Box 21)
      - Zu-LT-59 (J) 103-A-SE Zumpango-East (Box 21)
      - Zu-LT-60 (J) 103-A-SE Zumpango-East (Box 21)
      - Zu-LT-61 (J) 103-A-NE Zumpango-East (Box 21)
      - Zu-LT-62 (J) 103-B-NE Zumpango-East (Box 21)
      - Zu-LT-63 (J) 103-B-NE Zumpango-East (Box 21)
      - Zu-LT-64 (J) 103-B-SE Zumpango-East (Box 21)
      - Zu-LT-65 (J) 103-B-SE Zumpango-East (Box 21)
      - Zu-LT-66 (J) 104-B-NW Zumpango-East (Box 21)
      - Zu-LT-67 (J) 104-B-NW Zumpango-East (Box 21)
      - Zu-LT-68 (J) 104-B-NE, SE Zumpango-East (Box 21)
      - Zu-LT-69 (J) 102-G-SW, 102-H-NW Zumpango-East (Box 21)
      - Zu-LT-70 (J) 102-H-NE Zumpango-East (Box 21)
      - Zu-LT-71 (J) 102-H-NE Zumpango-East (Box 21)
      - Zu-LT-72 (J) 102-H-SW Zumpango-East (Box 21)
      - Zu-LT-73 (J) 102-H-SW, SE; 1012-I-NW Zumpango-East (Box 21)
      - Zu-LT-74 (J) 102-I-NE Zumpango-East (Box 21)
      - Zu-LT-75 (J) 102-I-NE Zumpango-East (Box 21)
      - Zu-LT-76 (J) I-L8-59B-SE Zumpango-East (Box 21)
      - Zu-LT-77 (J) I-L8-59C-NW Zumpango-East (Box 21)
      - Zu-LT-78 (J) I-L11-69A-SW Zumpango-East (Box 21)
      - Zu-LT-79 (J) I-L11-69A-SW Zumpango-East (Box 21)
      - Zu-LT-80 (J) I-L8-59B-SW Zumpango-East JRP 1973 (Box 21)
      - Zu-LT-81 (J) I-L12-60-NW Zumpango-East JRP 1973 (Box 21)
      - Zu-LT-82 (J) I-L14-70-SE Zumpango-East JRP 1973 (Box 21)
      - Zu-LT-83 (J) I-L14-70-NW Zumpango-East JRP 1973 (Box 21)
      - Zu-LT-84 (J) 108-B-NE Zumpango-East JRP 1973 (Box 21)
      - Zu-LT-85 (J) 105-B-SE 106-B-NE Zumpango-East (Box 21)
      - Zu-LT-86 (J) 105-A-SW Zumpango-East (Box 21)
      - Zu-LT-87 (J) 105-A-SW I-L10-1E-SE Zumpango-East (Box 21)
      - Zu-LT-88 (J) 105-E-SW Zumpango-East (Box 21)
      - Zu-LT-89 (J) 105-E-SW Zumpango-East (Box 21)
      - Zu-LT-90 (J) 105-F-NE Zumpango-East JP 1973 (Box 21)
      - Zu-LT-91 (J) 106-F-NW Zumpango-East (Box 21)
      - Zu-LT-92 (J) 106-F-NW Zumpango-East (Box 21)
      - Zu-LT-93 (J) 106-F-NW Zumpango-East (Box 21)
      - Zu-LT-94 (J) 106-F-W Zumpango-East (Box 21)
      - Zu-LT-95 (J) 106-F-SW Zumpango-East (Box 21)
      - Zu-LT-96 (J) 106-F-SW Zumpango-East (Box 21)
      - Zu-LT-97 (J) 106-D-NE Zumpango-East (Box 21)
      - Zu-LT-98 (J) 106-D-SW Zumpango-East JRP 1973 (Box 21)
      - Zu-LT-99 (J) 107-A-NW Zumpango-East (Box 21)
      - Zu-LT-100 (J) 107-A-SE Zumpango-East (Box 21)
      - Zu-LT-101 (J) 107-A-SE Zumpango-East (Box 21)
      - Zu-LT-102 (J) 107-C-SW Zumpango-East Mexico 1973 JRP (Box 21)
      - Zu-LT-103 (J) 107-C-SW Zumpango-East (Box 21)
      - Zu-LT-104 (J) 107-D-NE Zumpango-East (Box 21)
      - Zu-LT-105 (J) I-L11-61C-SE (Box 21)
      - Zu-LT-106 (J) I-L11-61D-SE Zumpango-East JRP 1973 (Box 21)
      - Zu-LT-107 (J) 107-B-NE Zumpango-East Mexico 1973 JRP (Box 21)
      - Zu-LT-108 (J) 107-B-SW Zumpango-East JRP1973 (Box 21)
      - Zu-LT-109 (J) 107-B-SE Zumpango-East Mexico 1973 JRP (Box 21)
      - Zu-LT-110 (J) I-L11-58B-NW Zumpango-East JRP 1973 (Box 21)
      - Zu-LT-111 (J) 109-B-NW Zumpango-East JRP 1973 (Box 21)
      - Zu-LT-112 (J) 109-A-SE Zumpango-East JRP 1973 (Box 21)
      - Zu-LT-113 (J) 109-B-NE 109-C-NW Zumpango-East JRP 1973 (Box 21)
      - Zu-LT-114 (J) 109-C-SE Zumpango-East JRP 1973 (Box 21)
      - Zu-Az-1 (J) I-L4-1A-NE Zumpango-East (Box 21)
      - Zu-Az-2 (J) I-L4-1A-NW Zumpango-East (Box 21)
      - Zu-Az-3 (J) I-L4-1A-SW Zumpango-East (Box 21)
      - Zu-Az-4 (J) I-L4-1A-NE Zumpango-East (Box 21)
      - Zu-Az-5 (J) I-L4-1A-SE Zumpango-East (Box 21)
      - Zu-Az-6 (J) I-L4-1B-NE Zumpango-East (Box 21)
      - Zu-Az-7 (J) I-L4-1B-SW Zumpango-East (Box 21)
      - Zu-Az-8 (J) I-L4-1B-SW Zumpango-East (Box 21)
      - Zu-Az-9 (J) I-L4-1B-SE Zumpango-East (Box 21)
      - Zu-Az-10 (J) I-L4-1B-SE Zumpango-East (Box 21)
      - Zu-Az-11 (J) I-L410-SW Zumpango-East (Box 21)
      - Zu-Az-12 (J) I-L4-10-NE, SE Zumpango-East (Box 21)
      - Zu-Az-13 (J) I-L4-1C-SW Zumpango-East (Box 21)
      - Zu-Az-14 (J) I-L4-1C-NW Zumpango-East (Box 21)
      - Zu-Az-15 (J) I-L3-44D-SE Zumpango-East (Box 21)
      - Zu-Az-16 (J) I-L3-44D-SW Zumpango-East (Box 21)
      - Zu-Az-17 (J) I-L3-44D-NW, I-L3-44C-SW Zumpango-East (Box 21)
      - Zu-Az-18 (J) I-L3-44C-SW Zumpango-East (Box 21)
      - Zu-Az-19 (J) I-L3-44C-SW Zumpango-East (Box 21)
      - Zu-Az-20 (J) I-L3-44B-SW Zumpango-East (Box 21)
      - Zu-Az-21 (J) II-L2-1D-SE Zumpango-East (Box 21)
      - Zu-Az-22 (J) II-L2-1D-SW Zumpango-East (Box 21)